https://biteable.com/privacy-policy/

Explore our video templates
Updated 12 November 2018 Your privacy is important to us, which is why we’ve created this Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy (together with our Terms of Use available at https://biteable.com/terms-of-use/ and any other documents incorporated by reference) sets out what information we collect about you, how we use the information we collect, how we share the information we collect, how we transfer your information internationally and how you can access and control your information. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your Personal Information and how we will treat it. Definitions In this Privacy Policy, the following definitions apply:
any reference to “Biteable”, “us”, “we” or “our” means Biteable Pty Ltd ACN 167 644 591; GDPR means the General Data Protection Regulation; Personal Information means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person and includes information that you provide to us directly, information that we collect from third parties and information that we collect from your device; Site means a site operated by us and includes each of https://biteable.com, https://app.biteable.com and any other domain that we may use from time to time.
How do we collect non-Personal Information? When you visit our Site, we collect non-Personal Information from you including, without limitation, which sections of the Site are most frequently visited, how often and for how long. This data is always used as aggregated, non-Personal Information. We may analyse this non-Personal Information and release it to third parties in an aggregated form. What Personal Information do we collect? We collect the following types of information about you: Information that you provide to us directly (A) Signing up to our service When you sign up to our service and set up an account, we collect the following information (which includes Personal Information) from you:
name; and email address.
(B) Making a purchase When you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect the following information (which includes Personal Information) from you:
name; email address; and credit card information (we don’t have access to your entire credit card number, CVC or billing address as this is handled by our payment gateway).
(C) Making a video When you use our services to create a video (“Video Content”), we collect the following information (which includes Personal Information) from you:
any photos, videos, audio and text content provided by you when creating Video Content.
(D) Additional information that we may ask for (optional) When you use our services, we may ask you to provide us with additional information. This additional information may include:
links to your social media accounts (including Facebook, Instagram, Twitter and YouTube); and information about your industry and the type of organisation you work for.
Information that we receive from third parties We may receive information about you (including Personal Information) from third parties.If you access our Site through a third-party connection or log-in, for example, through Facebook or Google, that third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to us. This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account, an access token necessary to access that third party service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information that you have made public in connection with that third party service. If you’d like to unlink your third party account from our Site, you can adjust your settings in the third party service and we will no longer receive information collected about you in connection with that service. Device information Like many websites, when you visit our Site, we automatically collect certain information through the use of “cookies”, web beacons, device identifiers, pixels and other technologies including information about your web browser, IP address and time zone. Some of this information may be classified as Personal Information. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”. We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier; “log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps; and “web beacons”, “tags” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
You can control or reset your cookies through you web browser and, if you choose to, you can refuse all cookies However, some of the features of our Site may not function properly if you disable the ability to accept cookies. How do we use your Personal Information? We use the information we collect about you for the following purposes:
Providing our products and services: We use the information that you provide to us to provide our products and services. This includes allowing you to create a Biteable account and to log in to your account, giving you access to your videos, recognising you across different services and devices and billing you for transactions that you make via our Site. Communicating with you: We use your contact information to send communications to you about important changes or updates to our products and services. When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, we also provide you with information or advertising relating to our products and services. Performing data analytics: We use the information about you to help us improve our products and services, including by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns. Customising our products and services for you: We use information about you to make sure that the Site and our products and services are customised to your needs. Keeping our Site secure: We use information about you to screen for potential risk and fraud, and to identify violations of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use. Where required by law: We will use or disclose your information where we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or a government authority; (b) to enforce our Terms of Use or to protect the security and integrity of our Site; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property or personal safety of Biteable, our customers or others. Where you have given your consent: We may seek your consent to use your information for a particular purpose. Where you give your consent for us to do this, we will use your information in accordance with that purpose. You can withdraw your consent to these uses at any time.
For Personal Information subject to the GDPR, we rely on the following legal bases to process this information:
where you have given your consent for us to use your information; where the processing is necessary to perform a contract that we have with you, for example when you purchase our products or services; ur legitimate business interests, such as improving and developing our products and services and marketing new features or products (but only where our legitimate interest isn’t overridden by your interest in protecting your Personal Information); and where it is necessary for compliance with our legal obligations.
You may at any time refuse to provide the Personal Information that we request. However, this may limit or prohibit our ability to provide our products and services to you. You may withdraw your consent for us to process your Personal Information at any time by contacting us in accordance with our “Contact us” section below. Who do we disclose Personal Information to? Outside of authorised personnel employed by us, we only share your Personal Information with third parties that meet the data privacy conditions described in this Privacy Policy. These third parties help us use your Personal Information, as described above, and include:
marketing platforms, communications platforms and contractors who we engage to help process Personal Information and other data; government third parties, including government agencies, regulatory bodies and law enforcement agencies as required, authorised or permitted by law; and a third party that acquires or intends to acquire Biteable or its assets.
International transfers of Personal Information Your Personal Information will be transferred to third parties including to persons and businesses outside Australia including in the United States of America and other countries where the privacy laws may not be as protective. These transfers are made in order to assist us to provide you with the products and services and/or to improve the products and services we offer you. When we transfer information to countries other than your own, we take reasonable steps to ensure that the recipients of such information do not breach the Australian Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) in relation to that information by entering into contractual arrangements with such third parties. International transfers of Personal Information (for users in the EEA) For our customers in the European Economic Area (EEA), where we transfer your Personal Information to a third party provider that is not located in the EEA and is not subject to an adequacy decision by the EU Commission, we will require those third party providers to enter into an agreement that provides appropriate safeguards for your information. From time to time we may also seek your consent to transfer your Personal Information to a third country outside the EEA. Changing or deleting your Personal Information You may update certain account information such as your name and email address by logging into your account and changing your profile settings. You can also stop receiving promotional email communications from us at any time by clicking on the “unsubscribe link” in the relevant communication. You may also access, review, update, rectify or delete your Personal Information by contacting us. We will respond to all requests within 30 days. Please note that deleting your Personal Information may limit our ability to provide the service to you We may limit or reject your request in certain cases, including without limitation where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy in the case question, where the rights of other persons would be violated or as required by law or governance purposes. If you need further assistance regarding your access and control of your Personal Information, please contact us. Security We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it (including encryption and password protection). Each of our employees is aware of our security policies, and your information is only available to those employees who need it to perform their jobs. However, no method of transmission over the Internet using industry standard technology is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your information. Data Retention When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Personal Information, and other personal information you have provided, for our records because we need this information to operate the accounts you have with us, to deliver our products and services to you and for the other purposes set out in the “What Personal Information do we collect?” section. We will retain this information unless and until you ask us to delete this information. Minors We do not knowingly advertise or collect Personal Information from any individual under the age of 13 and our services and content are not directed at children under the age of 13. For all users that are under the age of 16, we require the consent of a parent or legal guardian before that user can use our services. Our Terms of Use (available at https://biteable.com/terms-of-use/) has further details on this consent. If we later find out that we have collected Personal Information from any individual under the age of 16 without parental consent, we suspend and remove this Personal Information immediately. Links to other websites and services Our Site may allow access to third party content and services. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services accessible from the Site, including the information or content contained within these websites or services. When you use a link to go from our Site to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service that has a link or advertisement on our Site is subject to that third party’s own policies. Changes to our Privacy Policy We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy you will be notified via email (if we have your contact information) or otherwise in some manner through our services that we deem reasonably likely to reach you. Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon our publication of the new terms and/or upon implementation of the new changes to our services (or as otherwise indicated at the time of publication). In all cases, your continued use of our services or Site after the publication of any modified Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the terms of the modified Privacy Policy. Additional rights for EEA customers If you are a resident of the European Union for the purposes of the GDPR, then in addition to what is set out above, the following applies to you. Biteable is a data controller and processor for the purposes of the GDPR and by your consenting to this Privacy Policy Biteable is able to process your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In providing our products and services to you, we may make use of a number of automated processes using your Personal Information and your activity on our Site as tracked by us, in order to provide optimised services to you. In addition to your rights set out above, you may:
update or rectify any of the Personal Information we hold about you, in the manner described in the “Changing or Deleting your Personal Information” section above; withdraw your consent to our use of our Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. This can be done by contacting us directly, using the details set out in the “Contact us” section; request that we provide you with a copy of the Personal Information we hold about you in a portable and machine readable form or share your Personal Information with a nominated third party. This can be done by contacting us directly, using the details set out in the “Contact us” section.
If you are unhappy with our data practices, you also have a right to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory authority. Contact us Thank you for taking the time to read this. Please don’t hesitate to get in touch if you have any queries about the use of your private information — email us at legal@biteable.com or write to us at: Biteable Pty Ltd Level 2 162 Macquarie St Hobart TAS 7000 AUSTRALIA
Make a masterpiece in minutes
Join 7M+ marketers who have fallen in love with Biteable
Make a video — it’s free!
